Marcella Lucke, RN, BSN

Austin, Texas | www.linkedin.com/in/marcella-lucke | <u>luckemarcella@gmail.com</u>

Summary

I am a multifaceted professional with healthcare experience in the inpatient hospital setting. In this field, I found a passion for technology through Electronic Medical Record usage, and I decided further this knowledge by attending the Full Stack Coding Bootcamp at UT Austin. I love integrating the critical thinking I have learned in nursing with the complex nature of technology, and I look forward to pursing this innovative path in the future.

Education

Center for Professional Education, 2022 – University of Texas at Austin *Graduate of Full Stack Coding Bootcamp*

Saint Louis University, 2015 to 2019

Bachelor of Science in Nursing

Experience

Saint David's Medical Center, Travel Nurse, Operating Room, June 2022– Current

- Circulating nurse in the operating room with a focus on plastic surgery, general surgery, and robotics.
- Proficiently documented surgical procedures through Electronic Medical Records.
- Successfully communicated with team members to ensure patient safety.

Northshore Hospital, Registered Nurse, Operating Room June 2021–June 2022

- Circulated and scrubbed all service lines while maintaining sterile technique.
- Proficiently documented surgical procedures through Electronic Medical Records.
- Provided pre procedural patient and family education.

Northshore Hospital, Registered Nurse, Cardiac Step-Down Unit June 2019–June 2021

 Monitored patient condition, including interpreting and tracking EKG readings, identifying irregular telemetry readings and updating team members on changes in stability or acuity.

- Created assignments for oncoming shift and assisted staff as rotating charge nurse.
- Documented all patient interactions using Electronic Medical Records.
- Educated and advocated for patients and families throughout shift.

Northwestern Memorial Hospital, Student Nurse Intern, Trauma/Vascular Unit June 2018–Aug 2018

• Worked side by side an RN for three months to gain exposure to patient care at a world class hospital.

Skills

- Electronic Medical Records
- Critical Thinking
- Inpatient Care
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React
- MongoDB
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MySQL